<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rooney Jingyuan Gao</title>
    <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rooney Jingyuan Gao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 11:29:12 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rjgao1.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA-Shotchart</title>
      <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/nba-shotchart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 11:29:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/nba-shotchart/</guid>
      <description>An interactive dashboard for NBA player shot data.
Note: currently under maintaince as NBA has imposed CORS restrictions that prevent the package from being used in a browser directly
Work Summary   Built and deployed a dashboard using React JS, D3 and Ant Design to visualize NBA players&amp;rsquo; shot performance
  Improved user experience by adding 4 data filters and an autocomplete search bar providing player image preview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweety Pipe</title>
      <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/tweety-pipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 11:08:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/tweety-pipe/</guid>
      <description>A real-time data processor built with Spark and Kafka. Data visualized with a simple Flask app and Chart.js
Work Summary   Implemented a real-time data processor with Spark and Flask to visualize trending Twitter hashtags
  Designed and implemented a real-time sentiment monitor with Kafka, processing 3500 Tweets per minute
  Visualized results with Ajax and Chart.js for 1% of all public Tweets
  Technologies involved: Python, Spark, Kafka, Flask, Google Compute Engine, Twitter API</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/all-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 03:32:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rjgao1.github.io/projects/all-projects/</guid>
      <description>Tweety-Pipe: A Real-Time Data Processor with Spark and Kafka
NBA-Shortchart: An Interactive Visualization Dashboard for NBA player Shot Data
AFK, grabbing lunch, more to come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 02:20:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rjgao1.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>--  University of Toronto, St. George Honours Bachelor of Science Year 5
Upper-level CS GPA: 3.86/4.0
Year-4 &amp;amp; Year-5 GPA: 3.92/4.0
Specialist: Computer Science, Minors: Statistics, Math 09/2016 &amp;ndash; 06/2021
Courses include: Operating Systems, Software Engineering, Computer Networks, Deep Learning &amp;amp; Neural Networks, Statistical Methods for Machine Learning II, Intro. to Mobile Robotics, Intro. to Image Understanding, Algorithms &amp;amp; Data Structures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://rjgao1.github.io/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 22:07:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rjgao1.github.io/work/</guid>
      <description>--  Activision Blizzard - Demonware Demonware is an Activision Blizzard studio that provides online web services for some of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest video game franchises. Demonware&amp;rsquo;s services include matchmaking, in-game purchase, social networking and many more, producing 133,000+ metrics a second and impacting almost half a billion players&amp;rsquo; online gameplay experience.
Software Engineering Intern Call of Duty Modern Warfare, Warzone, Black Ops Cold War (WATCH THE TRAILER) 05/2020 &amp;ndash; 08/2020 Toronto, ON</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>